show.co 2016-06-17

# Privacy Policy · Show.co

Show.co, owned by Soundrop AS (“Soundrop”) a company registered in Norway under registration number 997 538 501 takes the matter of privacy very seriously, and treats all Personal Data with the utmost respect and in accordance with applicable privacy laws and regulations.

## General

  1. Soundrop’s Privacy Policy differs between Personal Data about the user of the Show.co service, having a direct commercial relationship with us (“Customer”, “You”), and Personal Data about the user of campaign sites or widgets as created by a user who is browsing the Site or Widget (“Consumers”).
  2. The term Personal Data does not include any anonymized and aggregated data made on the basis of Personal Data (“Aggregated Data”) which are wholly owned by Soundrop.

## Customer Personal Data

  1. Your Personal Data will be owned by You and used, processed and stored by Soundrop as a data controller. The Personal Data that You will provide to Soundrop by using the Service is Your name, the name of the legal entity You represent and Your email.
  2. Such Personal Data is collected, stored, used, and transferred only for the purposes of maintaining the customer relationship with You. Additionally, in some instances, we may also use Personal Data to send You information regarding update downloading, upgrades, enhancements, surveys, or advertisements.
  3. Soundrop has strict restrictions on access to Your Personal Data. Only a limited numbers of Soundrop employees have access.
  4. Soundrop uses certain third party services, including but not limited to Mixpanel and Intercom, for the purpose of serving and supporting our customers better, in addition to making improvements to the Service. We have privacy policy agreements in place with these services. You may read more about Mixpanel’ and Intercom’s privacy policies here:
  5. Mixpanel: [mixpanel.com/privacy/](https://mixpanel.com/privacy/)
  6. Intercom: [docs.intercom.io/privacy](http://docs.intercom.io/privacy)
  7. Soundrop uses third party server providers, and has adequate data processing agreements in accordance with applicable laws and regulations in place with them.
  8. You may change and modify Your Personal Data information at any time by logging to the service, and changing details in Your account profile.
  9. Soundrop deletes personal information when the purposes for the processing have been fulfilled.
  10. Procedures are reviewed regularly to ensure that the policies are followed. Any nonconformance, regarding the policies will be corrected without unnecessary delay.
  11. Soundrop has safeguards in place to protect Customers’ data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, alterations, or destruction. We protect user data from disclosure, with exceptions only in matters where designated by law or court order.
  12. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, we can be reached by email at: [legal@show.co](mailto:legal@show.co), or via mail at the following address:

**Soundrop AS**  
Inngang A1  
Sandakerveien 24C  
0473 Oslo  
Norway 

## Consumer Personal Data

  1. Soundrop shall operate as a data processor of the Personal Data collected about Consumers for our Customers, and will use, process, and store such Personal Data in accordance with applicable privacy laws and regulations.
  2. The Customer will be the data controller and therefore agrees to post maintain, and adhere to a privacy policy for any Personal Data collected at the external destination, such as a website, platform, service, form, or any other medium used to collect information on Consumers, which Show.co has been used to guide Consumers to, in full compliance with applicable laws and regulations. You furthermore agree that Soundrop may use the Personal Data of Your Consumers for the purposes of informing them about services offered through Show.co, and You shall procure that Your Consumers consents to the same in Your Privacy Policy.
  3. In the event You do not yet have a Privacy Policy, you may consider to apply the principles set out in this Privacy Policy by providing a reference (URL) to this Privacy Policy, but Soundrop disclaims any responsibility or liability if You choose to do so. As a data processor Soundrop will apply the same principles as set out in Section 2 above, and will by way of example only collect, store and process Consumer Personal Data for the express purpose of providing the Service, and to maintain necessary safeguards to protect Consumers’ data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, alteration, or destruction.

## Cookies

  1. We use a technology called “cookies” to enhance the user experience and to track patterns of behavior of visitors to the Sites that the Service is used with. This is done to provide and improve the Services we deliver, and to remember your settings and preferences between each session.
  2. Such data that our website sends to your browser is then stored on your system. You can set your browser to prevent this from happening, but this may reduce the quality and functionality of the Service. For information about how to prevent your browser from storing such data, please refer to your browser’s user manual.
  3. Our customers may use their cookies on our Service for the same general purposes as above. Third parties may use cookies or other similar technologies to collect information about you and your online activities. Most web browsers allow you to adjust your cookie preferences. For more information about the use of cookies and how to block them, visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) or [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

## Miscellaneous

  1. Soundrop is based in Norway, and this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of Norway without giving effect to any conflicts of law principles that may require the application of the laws of a different country.
  2. All actions or proceedings arising under or related to this Policy must be brought before the Oslo City Court, and each party hereby agrees to irrevocably submit to the jurisdiction and venue of any such court in all such actions or proceedings.
  3. If any provision of this Policy is determined by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, illegal, or unenforceable, the remaining provisions of this Policy shall not be affected or impaired thereby.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

  1. We may revise and amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. The date of the last update is always listed at the top of this document. Any updates to the information we collect and share will be reflected here. Soundrop is however, not responsible for giving notice about changes to the privacy policy, although Soundrop will use commercially reasonable efforts to inform You about material changes to this Privacy Policy.
